<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Pages>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>0</Achievement>
		<Content>Trogloids
    
      In the ancient times there was a gaseous planet called Ammoniaca, under squares and squares of gaseous ammonia there was a little solid sphere.

      And here, on this sphere, the great fuchsia menace born.
      Today, we know that Trogloid are a savage, non-intelligent race which uses Ammoniaca's sling effect on asteroids, to launch themselves in the space to colonize everything on their path.

      More accurate studies took our ancestors to discover two types of trogloids: Minion Trogloids and Troglothers.

      Minions are like us, but their brain is smaller and works like a radio: they can only receive orders by Troglothers.

      Troglothers instead are bigger and more aggressive, their screams can damage your ears, their eyes are as yellow as our sun!
      When a Troglother arrives on a planet, it is able to generate Minions, so watch out!
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>2</Achievement>
		<Content>Hominids
    
      Were do we come from?

      A long time ago, Hudda, a hominid who didn't believe in the Creation Theory, decided to isolate himself on a small moon and meditate until the real answer would be shown to him.

      when he returned home he was lost: holding a paper in his hand, his eyes were void and he kept repeating:
      "We're a mistake, we're a mistake!!"
      On this paper there was the declaration, written in a strange language, that the hominids were in fact, a mistake of a misterious programmer called Metalsoul, who just needed simple sprites for his game.

      That piece of paper took chaos on several planets, but since no more proofs about this theory were found, soon it was forgotten by everyone, except me.

      I still believe there is some truth but I hope I'm wrong...
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>4</Achievement>
		<Content>Creation

     Everything was born with a bang!
     Then, suddenly, wrong-coded gravity took all the matter to group in a single, perfectly spherical, planet.

     From the ground of this planet popped out a small line called Lato, and from the sky fell down on the ground another small line, Diagonale.

     From what we know, Lato and Diagonale decided to start a family, and their children were called Quadrato, Carr and Neli.

     The hominid race, as we all know, was the first one to appear in this universe, was born when Quadrato discovered that the world was in 3 dimensions, so he popped out his corners and they became vertices.
      
     And when he discovered what his brothers did, he divided himself into infinite cubes to find them, but each cube transformed during the journey and at the end no cube was identical to Quadrato.
      
     And this, is how all our races born, as far as we know.
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>5</Achievement>
		<Content>Resources
    
    Every engine or spaceship we know works with solar energy and is made of solid metallic keldanyum.
    
    Solar energy can be gathered trough solar panels and has an enormous potential.
    
    Keldanyum is a metallic mineral we extract from the ground, initially liquid, it solidifies as soon as it makes contact with the atmosphere.
    Keldanyum is everlasting, it doesn't oxidize with any atmosphere we know.
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>6</Achievement>
		<Content>Planetoid
    
    It's still a mistery from where the Planetoid comes.
    Every Planetoid is the same size as the previous, with the same force and power.
    Our ancestors thought it was pure anger coming from Lato and Diagonale, sent to destroy their children's horrible work.
    
    Some millenniums ago a heroic cube awaited the comet and jumped on it just before exploding with the planet.
    He studied the comet for long years and, as soon as the comet approached to another planet, he launched his research to another cube on the planet.
    The research is still discussed among the hominids for its strange contents:
    "Day 6, or maybe year? I can't remember.
    Today I discovered that the comet's tail is composed of an unknown material I named Barium.
    The surface is composed of high compressed Barium and I think it is so destructive just because Barium is more real than this world."
     
    Planetoid also seems to be the bridge between this world and another one, probably the same from where Barium comes from...
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>7</Achievement>
		<Content>Ships
    
    Hominids can't breathe in the emptiness of space, so they usually use spaceships to travel from planet to planet.
    Their spaceship-crafting ability refined in the ages and actually they only use two major types of spaceships:
     - The Hunter, a small and fast war spaceship, able to shoot lasers to damage enemy's structures.
     - The Rocket, a bigger spaceship, with a double-strength hull, capable of transporting multiple hominids to the destination.
     
    Both spaceships can be guided by every kind of hominids, but only pilots know how to use all the power of the engines!
    Hunters will also search for a free-space when landing, due to their fragile structure, which allows them to fly faster!
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>8</Achievement>
		<Content>Planets
    
      "Carr and Neli, in anger with their brother for his discovery, decided to divide the world into two perfect spheres to stay away from him.
      But as soon as they created those spheres, they found they weren't as perfect as the original, so they continued dividing the spheres and still now, somewhere, some new planets are being created by them."
      
      Nowadays we know that each planet is in fact, not perfect, the code can't use infinite vertices.
      Each planet is composed of 2 main parts: surface and core, the surface can produce 6 different atmospheres, but sometimes no one is produced.
      
      The core is white-hot and it's composed of liquid keldanyum, the core plus the planet's rotation produce a powerful pseudo-magnetic field.
      This field helps our vertices stick together and in fact we would explode if distant enough from a planet.
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>11</Achievement>
		<Content>Black Hole

     It is wrong to call those celestial bodies Black Holes, they don't act exactly like the real Black Holes, in fact they only attract solid keldanyum, not liquid one!

     Magnetic Wells, as we should call them, are highly magnetic points which attract solid keldanyum due to his positive charge, while Magnetic Well's is negative.

     If you look at the sky and you notice a distortion of the space, beware, that is a Magnetic Well!
     Be sure not to leave the planet while one of those bodies is around, the keldanyum-based ships would be immediately attracted by it. Remain on your planet!
      
     Planets have a negative magnetic field caused by the change of status of the keldanyum, this creates a sort of magnetic shield, which repulses Magnetic Wells.
     
     When a Magnetic Well has "sucked" enough keldanyum, the imbalance between the negative field and the positive field collapses and takes the Magnetic Well to nullify its magnetic point and all the keldanyum sucked suddenly transform into a sphere, a planet.
     Magnetic Well-formed planets don't have any kind of atmosphere, due to the lack of material in the sphere.
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>12</Achievement>
		<Content>Trivia
    
    Solar panels produce energy only if they can "see" the sunlight!
    Neither the programmer itself was able to convince a race to trade... uff
    One quest can't be completed if the music volume in the options is set to 0.
    You are invited to guess the programmer's favourite race.
    "Troglothed" asteroids are the equivalent of Planetoid 1/2 comets.
    The lore of this game is quite different from the one of Planetoid 3, due to the different developer of the title.
    The smoke sprite is the same since Planetoid 1!!
    If you sell a rocket while it is flying nearby a planet, there is the possibility to save the hominids!
    Gaseous atmospheres tend to deplete faster.
    Naive civilizations can answer to a message even 1 or 2 minutes later!
    The hunter acronym "KTA" stands for "Kill Them All"
    During the beta testing, a troglother's head performed 2 backflips!
    It is possible to detroy the planetoid.
    </Content>
	</Page>
	<Page>
		<Achievement>13</Achievement>
		<Content>Sun
    
    Every solar system has its own sun, a big nuclear reactor transforming material into pure energy.
    
    From what we know, a sun has a real long life, even if some years ago, in another sector of the known universe, suns used to collapse into enormous black holes and only nuclear power could return them to their previous state.
    
    Asteroids can't damage the Sun, the keldanyum they're composed of rapidly liquefies and generates an extremely hot flare on the Sun's surface.
    
    
    In some rare cases, it is possible to see the collision between a Planetoid and a Sun, the immense power of the Planetoid melts down in the Sun, causing it to overcharge its own burning reaction, increasing its volume and gravity.
    If your planet is not so far from an Overcharged Sun, hurry! Take a rocket and find a safer place!
    </Content>
	</Page>
</Pages>